This is your final warning.
（モニター音声:佐藤(さとう)）
これが最後の通告になる
This country...
（佐藤）
この国を 日本を明け渡せ
Give me Japan.
（ゲン）
これは 毒ガス弾？
This is poison gas!
（モニター音声:キャスター）
政府は全国民に
屋内退避を指示しましたが―
The government has instructed all citizens to take shelter indoors,
各地では
混乱が相次いでいるもようです
but signs of panic are appearing in every region.
What are you doing?
（田中功次(たなかこうじ)）
何やってんすか！
Doesn't this make it war for real?
（田中）
これじゃ
ホントに戦争じゃないすか！
（佐藤）
何を言ってるんだ 田中君
What are you saying, Tanaka-kun?
I’ve been saying from the beginning.
最初から言ってるだろ？
（佐藤）
これは戦争だって
That this is war!
（高橋(たかはし)）
佐藤のやつ 完全に狂ってやがる…
That fuck Satou,
he’s completely off his rocker.
（ゲン）
これからどうする？
But... what will we do now?
As for that, I have an idea.
（奥山(おくやま)）
それなら考えがある
（中野攻(なかのこう)）
永井(ながい)！
Nagai!
（下村泉(しもむらいずみ)）
あ…
（戸崎優(とさきゆう)）
なぜ 戻った？
Why did you come back?
Isn’t it obvious?
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
決まってるだろ
佐藤を止めるには
僕の力が必要なはずだ
In order to stop Satou, you need me.
Don’t fuck with me!
（戸崎）
ふざけるなっ！
今のお前に何が出来る！？
What can you do now?
あんたが僕のことを
信用してないのは分かってるし―
I know you don’t trust me.
そんなことはどうでもいい
I don’t care about that.
でも…
But...
I will stop Satou.
僕は佐藤を止める
That’s what I ought to do.
そうするべきだ
Nagai-kun!
（泉）永井君！
（攻）お前！
You-
（爆発音）
（戸崎）あっ
（攻）あっ
（泉）あっ
It- It’s an explosion!
（キャスター）
ば… 爆発です
Could it be the Self-Defense Force base that
Satou is occupying?
（キャスター）
亜人 佐藤の占拠している
自衛隊基地内でしょうか？
All of a sudden,
it seems there’s been an explosion!
突如として爆発したもようです！
They’re really making a show out of it.
（オグラ・イクヤ）
派手にやってるな
（携帯の着信音）
（戸崎）ちっ
Yes.
はい
（奥山）
話がしたい
I want to talk.
♪目を醒せ　このdistiny♪
Me o samase seou destiny, nogarerarenai no nara
Open your eyes Take on destiny If you can’t escape
♪逃れられないのなら♪
♪正しさも過ちも
全てを飲み込み闘う♪
Munashisa mo ayamachi mo, Subete o nomikomi tatakau
The futility and mistakes take them all in and fight
Zawameku kokoro no yami o tsukasadoru kyoui
Menace rules the darkness of the murmuring heart
♪騒(ざわ)めく　心の闇を
司(つかさど)る脅威♪
♪理性を　失くしかけてる
人間の真理♪
Risei o nakushikaketeru, ningen no shinri
Human psychology almost losing rationality
♪僕は知る　その無意味さを♪
Boku wa shiru  Sono muimisa o
I know how meaningless it is
♪偽りの平穏さえ　砕け散るなら♪
Itsuwari no heion sae kudakechiru darou
If only the tranquility of lies is smashed up
♪抗(あらが)う影　落とす♪
Aragau kage o toosu
Fight through the opposing shadow
♪It's the end of escape
立ち上がる♪
The end of escape, tachiagaru, sono michi shika nai kara
The end of escape, Make a stand, That’s the only way
♪その道しかないから♪
Tadoritsuke boku ga mezashita chiisana sono kibou ni
Struggle towards that tiny hope I aimed for
♪辿り着け　僕が目指した
小さなその希望に♪
♪差し伸べた　その手から♪
Sashinobeta sono te kara, koboreochita yowasa wa
The weakness spilling over from that outstretched hand
♪零れ落ちた弱さは♪
Orokashisa mo ayamachi mo subete o nomikomi kurutta
The foolishness and mistakes, I’ve gone mad taking them all in
♪正しさも過ちも
全てを飲み込み狂った♪
It sounds interesting,
so I guess it’s okay.
（米軍現場司令官）
くっ…
回収は終了した　探索に入れ
We’ve finished collecting the missiles.
Begin the search.
（米軍兵士）
了解
Roger.
（米軍現場司令官）
何としてでも捕獲しろ
Bring him in at any cost.
我々をコケにすればどうなるか
思い知らせるんだ
We can’t let him make fools out of us.
We’ll teach him a lesson.
（佐藤）
やつらはコケにされるのが
何よりも嫌いだからねぇ
They hate being made fools of
more than anything else.
これで本気になるはずだよ
This should make them get serious.
ふーん いやあ
楽しみだねぇ 田中君
This is fun, isn’t it, Tanaka-kun.
はぁ…
米軍怒らせて そんなこと言えんの
佐藤さんくらいっすよ
You’re probably the only one who can say antagonizing
the U.S. military is fun, Satou-san.
（田中）
でも あの殺人ガス
手放しちゃってよかったんすか？
But that lethal gas,
did you intend to let go of it?
Killing unresisting opponents with
poison gas is boring.
毒ガスで無抵抗なやつら殺しても
面白くないだろ？
If they don’t come at you with the
intent to kill, it’s no fun!
（佐藤）
殺す気で来るやつらじゃないと
殺しがいがない
（田中のため息）
（下水が流れる音）
（米軍兵士）
こちら探索チーム
This is the search team.
We’ve found Satou’s escape route.
（スピーカー音声:米軍兵士）
佐藤の逃走経路を発見
すぐに支援チームを送る
We’ll send a support team soon.
（米軍副官）
大佐 ペンタゴンからです
Commander.
It’s the Pentagon.
Hello.
はい
Yes.
ええ 全機無事に
All the missiles are safe.
We’re starting the search immediately.
既に探索に入り…
Eh-
え？
い いや しかし
そんなことをすれば…
No, but-
If you do that-
わ… 分かりました　では
Understood.
Very well.
（携帯を切る音）
（ため息）
（米軍副官）
どうされました？
What did they say?
（ため息）
首相官邸につないでくれ
Connect me to the Prime Minister.
（コウマ）
あ…
つ つまり―
In short,
the plan is to release the recovered nerve gas
underground, and render Satou powerless?
回収した神経ガスを
地下に散布し―
佐藤を
無力化するということですか？
Capture Satou, and clean up this situation.
（官房長官）
佐藤を捕獲し
事態を収拾するには―
それしかないと判断された
It was decided that that’s the only way.
But...
（コウマ）
しかし その作戦では―
if we do that, it will take an enormous amount
of time to evacuate the citizens,
住民の避難に
膨大な時間がかかり―
その間に逃走される恐れも…
and he could escape during that-
No-
（官房長官）
いや…
In order to avoid alerting Satou,
we can’t evacuate the citizens.
（総理大臣）
佐藤に察知されるのを防ぐため―
住民を避難させることは出来ない
（曽我部(そかべ)）
ま 巻き添えにすると
いうのですか！？
So they’re collateral damage?
（官房長官）
当然 佐藤のテロとして処理される
全ての罪はやつが負うことにな…
Of course, we can treat it as part of
Satou’s terrorism.
He’ll become responsible for all
wrongdoing.
（机をたたく音）
（コウマ）体裁の問題じゃない！
This isn’t about outward appearances!
How can you think about the
citizens this way?
国民をいったい
何だと思っとるんだ
The truth is, we have already transferred
control to the U.S. army.
事実上の指揮権は
既に米軍に移っている
We have no right to veto the plan.
我々に拒否権は無い
そんな…
It can’t be...
（ため息）
作戦決行まで７時間ある
We have seven hours until the plan goes into action.
それまでに佐藤を捕獲すれば
散布は無い
If we capture Satou before then,
the gas won’t be released.
That is the only option we have.
（官房長官）
それが 我々が勝ち取れた
唯一のオプションだ
No, but...
（曽我部）いや しかしですね…
（官房長官）言ったはずだぞ
Haven’t I said?
（官房長官）
これは 君ら管理委員会が
やつを野放しにし続けた結果だと
This is the result of your Ajin Management Committee's
failure to take care of Satou!
くっ…
（車が走る音）
（ドアを開ける音）
また ここですか…
Back here again?
（足音）
There’s no need to be on your guard.
（奥山）
警戒する必要はないよ
We’re not planning to lure you into a trap.
（奥山）
わなに はめようなんて
思ってないから
なぜ 僕らにコンタクトを？
Why did you contact us?
You took on Satou-san twice and
are still here to tell the tale.
（奥山）
君は佐藤さんと２回も対じして
まだ生きてる
We simply judged that this was the
only place of resistance.
（奥山）
唯一の対抗馬だと
判断したまでだよ
佐藤さんを止めるのに
力を貸したい
We want to lend our power to stop Satou-san.
And in return?
見返りは？
佐藤さんは―
Satou-san isn’t one to let traitors live.
裏切り者を生かしておくような
人じゃないからね
そちらは３人だけですか？
Just three people on your side?
There were more at Musashi Heavy Industries.
武蔵(むさし)重工の時は
もっといましたよね？
Everyone else fled.
みんな逃げたよ
佐藤さんと戦うなんて
正気じゃないってね
They said that it was insane to
fight back against Satou.
僕も同意見ですね
I have to agree.
（圭）
田中さんもですか？
Tanaka-san too?
いや あの人は…
No, he-
-stayed with Satou-san, didn’t he.
佐藤さんのとこに残ったんですね？
（高橋）
どうでもいいだろ んなことは
Who cares about him.
In order to stop Satou,
your only choice is to team up with us.
佐藤を止めてぇなら
俺たちと組むしかねぇんだよ
（ゲン）
田中さんの言ったとおり
イケ好かないガキだね
Like Tanaka-san said,
you’re a pretty disagreeable kid.
黙れ クズどもが
Be quiet, you scum.
There’s no way we can easily trust
terrorists like you!
貴様らみたいなテロリストを―
簡単に信用出来るわけが
ないだろう
What?
（高橋）
あ！　何だと この野郎！
What did you just say, you bastard?
俺たちをこうしたのは―
We’re only like this
because all of you wanted to use us ajin
as animals for experimentation!
てめぇらが 亜人を
実験動物扱いしたからだろうが！
あ…
（銃を抜く音）
What will you do?
どうするの？
組むの？　組まないの？
Join us? Or no?
（携帯の着信音）
Hang on a minute.
ちょっと待て
（戸崎）
はい
Yes.
Shall we make a deal?
（曽我部）
取引しませんか 先輩
Senpai.
お… 曽我部！？
Sokabe.
A somewhat unfavorable situation has arisen.
いささか まずい事態が
持ち上がりましてね
（戸崎）
さっさと用件を言ったらどうだ
Tell me your conditions immediately.
Tsk!!
ちっ こんな時に長電話かよ
A long phone call at a time like this?
（戸崎）
ふぅ… お前ら
佐藤の居場所は知ってるのか！？
You all.
Do you know where Satou-san is?
（奥山）
地下の隠れ家にいるはずだよ
He should be in the hiding place underground.
Come with me.
（戸崎）
ついて来い！
（高橋）ああ？
（圭）は？
What?
What are you doing?
何をやってる！？
ぼやぼやするな！
Don’t dilly-dally.
（車が走る音）
（足音）
Izumi-san. Welcome back!
（攻）
泉さん おかえり
（ドアが開く音）
（ドアを閉める音）
Are we really joining forces with
the terrorists?
ホントにテロリストと組むのか？
ああ 他に選択肢は無いし
時間も無い
Yes.
We have no other choice,
and there’s no time.
（トラックの開く音）
This is Takahashi-san, Gen-san, and Okuyama-san.
高橋さんにゲンさん 奥山さんだ
Yo.
うっす
はぁ…
あっ！
Genocide.
大量虐殺だよ
（ゲン）フッ
（高橋）ハハハ…
（消防士）うわっ！
（攻）おっさん！
Pops!
Got ‘em!
（高橋）
当たったぞ
お前らかっ！　こんの野郎！
おりゃあっ！
You’ll pay for that!
Idiot!
（圭）
おい 馬鹿 やめろ！
Stop it!
Where’s Pops?
おっさん どこだ？
どこに隠しやがった？
Where did you hide him?
お 落ち着けよ
Hey, calm down.
We let him go.
あいつらなら解放したぞ
Huh?
は そうなの？
Really?
Yeah.
（ゲン）
ああ 今頃 家族んとこだろ
He’s probably with his family now.
You got it now? Stupid kid.
分かったか 馬鹿ガキ
What do you mean, stupid!
（攻）馬鹿ってなんだ この野郎
（圭）だからやめろって！
Stop it!
Like I’m gonna let you-
（もめる声）
Nagai!
Look what happens with all these
ajin in one place.
まさか これだけの亜人が
１カ所に集まるとはな
It’s almost like a harem.
（オグラ）まるでハーレムだ
（鈴村(すずむら)）フッ
（ドアが開く音）
ああ そっちは任せる
Yes.
Leave that to me.
（もめる声）
Cut it out, you guys!
（戸崎）
いいかげんにしろ お前ら！
さっさと中に入れっ！
Hurry up and get inside!
Ah, wait a minute.
（奥山）
あ ちょっと待って
あ？
Oh!
（トランクを開ける音）
（奥山）
気にいってもらえると
いいんだけど
I hope you’re happy with these.
（攻）おおっ…
If we do this, we’ve got to make it showy.
やるからには
派手にいかないとね
（パソコンを打つ音）
At present the U.S. military is closing off this sphere,
現在米軍は
自衛隊駐屯地を中心にして―
with the Self-Defense Force garrison at its center.
この範囲を封鎖している
（戸崎）
やつらは
この地域全域を犠牲にして―
They plan to sacrifice all the people
in this area, and capture Satou.
佐藤を捕獲するつもりだ
ぎ 犠牲にするって…
Sacrifice, as in...
They’re releasing the nerve gas underground.
地下に神経ガスを散布するんだ
It’s only natural that tens of thousands of people
will be sacrificed in the process.
当然 数万人単位の犠牲者が出る
（攻）
なっ…
決行は午前３時
The plan will be carried out at 3 a.m.
About four hours remain.
残りは約４時間だ
その前に 何としてでも
佐藤を捕獲する　いいな？
Before then, we have to capture Satou at any cost!
Got it?
（攻）
ああ 当たり前だ
Yeah.
Obviously!
However, the Anti-Ajin Special Forces are
also moving to stop Satou.
（泉）
ただし 対亜人特選群も
佐藤確保に動いています
We have to execute a plan that
it won’t conflict with theirs.
（泉）
それとかち合わずに作戦を
遂行することが前提になります
（圭）
では 作戦ですが―
Then, as for a plan,
これは奥山さんが作成した
東京の地下道の地図です
this is the map that Okuyama-san put together
of the underground tunnels in Tokyo.
Satou-san’s hideout is here.
（圭）
佐藤さんのアジトはここ
Satou-san is calling the U.S. forces here,
and plans to fight.
佐藤さんは ここに米軍を
呼び込んで たたくつもりだった
In other words,
（圭）
つまり
何が来ても迎え撃てる準備を―
no matter who comes,
整えているということです
he’s getting ready to face them.
佐藤は いったい
何をたくらんでる？
What on earth is Satou planning?
市民権も独立国家も
でたらめだった
Civil rights and an independent nation,
both of those things were no good.
やつの目的は何だ？
What’s his objective?
（うなる声）
（奥山）
戸崎さんはゲームやる時―
Tosaki-san, when you play games,
“お姫様を助けるぞ”って
気分でやる？
is it because you’re excited to save Princess Peach?
Huh?
は？　何だ それは？
What are you talking about?
Sure, you need a story,
ストーリーは必要だけど―
“亀を踏み潰すのが楽しい”から
やるんでしょ？
but you’re playing because it’s fun
to jump on turtles, aren’t you?
No idea. I don’t play video games.
（戸崎）
知らんな　私はゲームなどやらん
He means that Satou’s a simple person.
佐藤さんは
単純な人ってことですよ
He’s not a revolutionary or a tactician.
あの人は革命家でも策士でもない
He’s just a player.
ただの遊び人です
And that’s exactly why we have room
to take advantage of him.
（圭）
だからこそ つけいる隙が
あるんです
What do you plan to do?
どうするつもりだ？
Bury him alive.
生き埋めにする
（ゲームの音）
Tanaka-kun.
（佐藤）
田中君 そっちの敵は任せたよ
I’m leaving that enemy to you.
Ah, hold on, it’s too sudden-
（田中）
え いや そんな 急に言われても…
Ah... I died.
あ… 死んだ
（佐藤）
フッ 射撃同様
君は全然うまくならないねぇ
You just don’t get any better
at shooting, do you.
I’m sorry I’m so bad!
（田中）
すいませんねぇ 下手くそで
（圭）はっ はっ…
（攻）はっ はっ…
（泉）はっ はっ…
（警告音）
（田中）あっ…
Ah, we have guests.
おお お客が来たよ
A midnight party, I suppose.
（佐藤）
真夜中のパーティーってとこだね
（足音）
Ah, this really gets you going!
（佐藤）
いやあ わくわくするねぇ
何しろ相手は 世界最強の軍隊だ
As you know, our opponent is the strongest
armed force in the world.
（佐藤）
きっちり おもてなししないとね
We have to give them a warm welcome.
Was this your goal from the beginning?
最初から
これが目的だったんすか？
（佐藤）
ん？
Hm?
いや…
I mean,
to lure out the U.S. government.
米軍 引きずり出すのが
だから
俺を助けたり仲間集めたり―
And that’s why you saved me, and gathered
associates, and did all that terrorism.
テロ起こしたりしたんすか？
違うよ
Not at all!
If you know what the last boss is from the beginning, where’s the fun?
最初から 誰がラスボスか
分かってたら面白くないだろ？
I see.
はあ
じゃあ これで終わりなんすか？
Then, this is the end?
What?
（佐藤）
え？
あ… いや ラスボス倒したら
終わりなんすよね ゲームって？
I mean, if we beat the last boss, that’s the end, isn’t it.
For a game.
Ha!
かぁっ 何を言ってるんだ 田中君
What are you saying, Tanaka-kun?
The real thrill of games starts with
the second playthough.
ゲームのだいご味は
２周目からだよ
（ドアを蹴破る音）
Excuse me.
（圭）すいませんね
（佐藤）え？
For stepping in on your fun.
お楽しみのところ邪魔しちゃって
（田中）
あっ…
Nagai-kun, was it.
永井君だったのか
That was fast.
早いな よくここが分かったね
I’m surprised you found this place.
Even in the sewers,
下水に潜っても―
人殺し野郎の臭いは
隠せませんからね
you can’t hide the smell of a murderer.
ああ 奥山君たちか…
Ah, it was Okuyama-kun and the others.
That certainly was beyond my expectations.
さすがにそれは想定外だったな
But anyhow,
（佐藤）
でも まあ
面白そうだからいいけどね
it sounds interesting, so I guess it’s okay.
（圭）
これはもっと面白いですよ
This is even more interesting.
The U.S. army that you’re waiting for...
佐藤さんが待ってる米軍ですが…
ところで永井君 覚えてるかな？
By the way, Nagai-kun, do you remember?
Didn’t I tell you,
I hate people getting in my way?
私は 邪魔をされるのが
嫌いだと言ったの
Who knows.
さあね
But Satou-san,
でも 佐藤さんだって―
you’re getting in my way-
僕の人生を邪魔して…
覚えているかと聞いてるんだっ！
I’m asking if you have a good memory!
Answer the question!
（佐藤）
質問に答えろっ！
There are three ways to strike a person like Satou.
佐藤さんのような人を
たたく方法は３つだ
Number one- provocation.
１ 挑発
（圭）く… 来るぞ！
（銃撃の音）
Incoming!
Go, ghost!
（圭）
行け 幽霊！　殺せ！
Kill!
Number two- diversion.
２ けん制
（圭ＩＢＭ）
すいませんね！
（佐藤ＩＢＭ）
残念　外れだ
Too bad.
You missed.
（押し倒す音）
（銃撃の音）
（攻）がっ！
（泉）ぐっ…
幽霊っ！
Ghost!
（田中）
な 連続で？
In a row?
（佐藤）
相変わらず すごいねぇ
You’re as impressive as ever.
Number three-
３ 僕という脅威の周知と―
pretend we’re scared,
and run away.
逃走
くっ いったん引くぞ
Fall back for now!
（攻）がっ…
（泉）ぐっ…
Today I won’t let you go.
今日は逃がさないよ
はぁっ… はぁっ… はぁっ…
If we can lure Satou to this point,
この場所まで
佐藤さんを誘導出来れば―
あとは天井を爆破して
生き埋めにするだけです
then all that’s left is to explode the
ceiling, and bury him alive.
なるほどね
I see.
生き埋めにすれば
何度 復活しても動けない
Once he’s buried alive, he can’t move no matter
how many times he revives.
Exactly.
そう 僕らの勝ちです
That's our chance..
（田中）
ああっ
はぁっ… はぁっ…
（追いかける足音）
もっかいだ 幽霊っ！
One more time, ghost!
Fight to the death to stop him!
死ぬ気で止めろ！
I know that!
（圭ＩＢＭ）
分かってるよ！
That bastard!
あの野郎 何体 出せるんだ！？
How many of those can he produce?
Nagai-kun’s black stuff- there’s a lot of it.
永井くんの黒いのは
量が多いからねぇ ハハッ
（押し倒す音）
（田中）
おおっ…
ハハハッ だとしても
同時には出せない
But even so,
he can’t bring out more than one at a time.
（圭）
ああ くそっ 押さえ込まれた
Shit!
It’s been immobilized!
I can’t use my ghost for while!
Hurry!
しばらく幽霊は使えない！　急げ！
The remaining problem is making sure
Satou-san doesn't catch you, right.
（奥山）
残る問題は 君たちが佐藤さんに
追い付かれないか だね
（圭）
幽霊で何とかしますよ
With my ghost, I’m sure we can manage somehow.
Your way of planning and train of thought
is exactly the same as Satou’s,
君は 作戦の立て方とか思考回路は
佐藤さんそっくりだけど―
but you have a poor endgame.
詰めが甘い部分だけは違うね
（銃声）
（圭）がぁっ…
（圭のうめき声）
（攻）
永井！
Nagai!
（圭のうめき声）
Oh well.
（奥山）
仕方ないな　僕が保険を掛けるよ
I’ll provide you some insurance.
No... problem!
問題… ない
（ドローンが飛ぶ音）
Let’s go!
（圭）
行くぞ！
（佐藤）はっ
（田中）ああっ
（ドローンが飛ぶ音）
Is this a parting, Okuyama-kun.
やっぱり 君か 奥山君
It was fun playing together.
一緒にいろいろやったのは
楽しかったんですけどね
I’m sorry.
すいません
（キーを押す音）
（爆発音）
（銃声）
フフッ 自慢のおもちゃを悪いな
奥山
Sorry about your toys, Okuyama.
Ah, when did you get so good?
（佐藤）
ほう いつの間に
そんなにうまくなったんだい？
You can do anything with practice.
（田中）
“何事も練習”ですよ
行きますか？
Shall we go?
ああ コンティニューだ
Select ‘Continue’.
（一同）
はっはっはっ…
We got away, Nagai.
（攻）
見えたぞ 永井
Just a little more.
（攻）
あと少しだ
（銃撃の音）
（泉）来た
They’re here.
Kuro-chan!
（泉）クロちゃん…
（圭）待って
Wait.
Don’t stop him unnecessarily.
下手に足止め… しないほうがいい
（銃撃の音）
（泉）ああっ
（攻）ああっ
（銃声）
At this rate...
we’re almost there!
このまま 突っ切る！
（佐藤の笑い声）
（佐藤）
亜人ならではだねぇ ヘヘッ
This kind of fun you can only have with ajin.
（爆発音）
（佐藤）なに？
What?
To continue our talk from earlier-
（圭）
さっきの話の… 続きですけどね…
佐藤さん！
Satou-san!
（佐藤）
えぇ？
いつまで待っても…
米軍は来ませんよ
You can wait as long as you want,
but the U.S. forces aren’t coming!
やつら…
They plan to do you in with nerve gas!
神経ガスで
あんたを無力化する気ですから！
（佐藤）
ああ…　冗談だろ？
You’re joking, right?
Everyone’s fed up with playing your games!
みんな…
あんたの遊びに付き合うのには…
もう うんざりしてるんですよ！
（携帯のボタンを押す音）
（爆発音）
（佐藤）なにっ！
What?
（田中）
うわっ
Burying us alive...
（佐藤）
生き埋めか…
Satou-san!
（田中）
佐藤さん！
You put some thought into it.
考えたな
But... just when you thought you’ve won...
でも―
勝ったと思った瞬間―
The rug gets pulled out from under you!
人は足をすくわれるんだ
（爆発音）
（瓦礫が崩れる音）
（圭）
はぁっ…
はぁ…
Alright. I’ll go contact Sokabe.
よし
曽我部に連絡を入れてくる
（爆発音）
（一同）あっ…
What?
な 何だ？
No way!
まさか！
（鈴村）崩落か？
（高橋）やりすぎたのかよ
Are they digging in?
We overdid it!
（圭）
いや 床が！
No, the floor-
It’s going down!
（攻）落ちる
（泉）戸崎さん！
（泉）
あっ！うっ…
あっ ああっ！
（高橋）
うわぁ
（攻）うわぁ…
（圭）うわっ ああ…
Less than 35 minutes remain.
（オペレーター）
残り時間 35分を切りました
（曽我部の舌打ち）
（２人のため息）
（佐藤）
君たち全員ブチ殺してやる
I’ll kill... every last one of you!
はっ！
（銃を構える音）
（戸崎のうめき声）
Tosaki-san!
（泉）
はっ！　戸崎さん！
大丈夫ですか！？
Are you alright?
（瓦礫を持ち上げる音）
（泉）
はっ…
はっ！
（足音）
ゲーム スタートだ
Game... start!
（銃声）
To be continued...
Mou akitakara koukan shiyou
Since I'm tired of it, let's exchange it
♪もう飽きたから交換しよう♪
Omae ga motteru futsuu no to
With the normal one that you are holding
♪お前が持ってる普通のと♪
Kira kira shiteru kami no kaado to
A shining paper card and
♪キラキラしてる神のカードと♪
Zara zara shiteru kami no kaado
A rough paper card
♪ザラザラしてる紙のカード♪
Kondo uchi ni kitara
Next time you come to my house
♪今度家に来たら♪
Zenbu miseteyaru yo dakara
I'll show you everything, so...
♪全部見せてやるよ♪
♪だから♪
Koutei no sumi ni futari, kaze ga fuite ima
At the edge of the schoolyard the wind blows...
♪校庭の隅に二人 風が吹いて♪
♪今なら言えるかな♪
nara ieru ka na?
can I say it now?
Dare nimo iwanai kotoba
Words never spoken to another person
♪誰にも言わない言葉♪
Yasashiku suru kara asobi ni kite yo
I'll be gentle so come and play often
♪「優しくするから
遊びに来てよ」♪
Nandemo ageru yo, ne
I'll give you anything, hey
♪「何でもあげるよ ねぇ」♪
Korekara zutto tomodachi de ite yo
Let's be friends forever
♪「これからずっと
友達でいてよ」♪
Preview
Next week’s episode will air at 3:10 a.m.
I make promises too,
Satou-san.